Wealth, Fame, Power.
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer,
and his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it.
These words lured men to
the Grand Line and pursued
dreams greater than they'd
ever dared to imagine.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era.
I'm going to be a dream of my dreams.
I'm going to find a new one.
One Piece.
The rushing run is a tank of water.
I'm going to be able
to get rid of the heat.
I'm just trying to do this to me.
I'm not still trying to do this to me.
I'm not sure how to do this?
What happened to me?
I'm not sure
how to do that.
I'm going to be a dream.
I'm going to be looking for a dream.
I'm going to be a pocket coin.
So you wanna be my friend?
We are, we are wanna do!
We are!
Stop it, Soul!
You're scaring me!
Hope you're ready, cause if
you make an enemy out of me,
there's gonna be hell to be!
What's going on?
It's Vice Admiral Sol!
He ran away with Nico Olvia
and now he's attacking us!
He's lost his mind!
What's he doing on Oma?
How do I know?
The whole island is done for!
They're gonna burn it to the ground!
Don't give up yet!
Even if the library burns,
we can still save the books!
Throw them out the window
and drop them in the lake!
They're better off wet than burn to ash!
Hurry up!
Fire!
Come back! Don't do this!
It's not like you!
Get all the books out of the library!
Don't give up on a single book!
Don't give up on a single sentence!
These words have been passed
on for thousands of years!
They must reach the future!
Robin!
Get the heck out of here!
The evacuation ship's
gonna leave without you!
Don't worry about me, just run!
Oh, my God.
Sonny!
Shoot him down!
Come on! Go! Get moving!
Don't you remember what your mom told you?
You must live, Robin!
Attention evacuees!
The ship is leaving!
Wait!
Someone's coming!
It's her!
Isn't that the monster girl?
Yeah, it is.
Go away, you're creepy!
Hey, now's not the time for that.
Now wait, that kid's mother Ovia was
in the newspaper just the other day.
That means she's the
daughter of a criminal.
You're right, if we let her on the
ship it might cause us trouble.
Just leave her.
Don't be ridiculous, she's just
a child, hurry up and help her.
Everyone stop, don't
let that brat on board.
She may be a child, but
she's still an archaeologist.
That means she's a criminal
like the rest of them.
A little girl like that?
If you say so, Chief. See? I told you.
Good thing we didn't let her on.
Robin!
Must be CP9. Damn.
I'll show them. Chief!
Vice Admiral Saul is coming this way!
Is that so?
Then there was no need to question
Olvia about him after all.
Fire! Now! Shoot him down!
Ice block!
Partisan!
It's Kuzan!
You.
My, my, my.
This just won't do.
If we let a former Marine stop the
Buster Call, we'd look like damn fools.
Kuzan, wake up!
You can't tell me this
nonsense is justice!
Pull back now!
You know this ain't right.
They're just making an
example out of O 'Hara.
Come on, please.
You're better than this.
If it's for the good of the
world, it has to be done.
You can't deny that those scholars
are breaking the law, can you?
I won't criticize your sense of justice.
There are as many rights and wrongs
as there are viewpoints in the world.
However, if you insist on getting in our
way, I can't sit back and do nothing.
The evacuation ship was blown up what
happened looks like cannon fire from
one of our ships it Was vice admiral
sakazuki that idiot if we're doing this
we have to be thorough if even one Of
those scholars had managed to sneak on
board that ship then all the sacrifices
we made today They would be in vain.
However small, we cannot
allow any evil to thrive.
Is this what you call justice?
Can you take pride in something like this?
We went too far.
I would never do something like that.
We gotta run, Robin.
This fellow's way too
strong for me to fight.
Sol is escaping.
He's taking one of the scholars with him.
Ice time, capsule.
Oh, no!
Sol, are you okay?
Robin, you gotta get out of here.
Don't look back. Just go.
If you stay on this island, you'll die.
Take my raft and go out to sea.
But what about you?
He's got me, little lady.
I'm afraid this is the end.
Hurry! No!
Everybody I care about is here!
Now you listen to me.
You may be lonely at first, but
one day you'll find true friends.
True friends?
Yeah, the sea's a vast
place, so I guarantee.
Someday you'll find friends
who won't ever leave you.
No matter who you are, ain't no one
born into this world will be alone.
It's time to go Robin.
This is goodbye.
When things are bad, do like I taught you.
You remember the laugh, don't you?
Look out!
He's behind you!
Now, ice time.
Oh, no!
Your friends are out there at
sea waiting for you, Robin.
All you gotta do is find them.
Share your life with them
and never let them go.
This is it.
We're done for.
So this is the history
that mankind has chosen.
Shall we ever learn the error of our legs?
Forgive me.
Robin, I couldn't even leave
you with any parting words,
neither as a scholar or a mother.
A tree of knowledge.
It's falling.
The concept of absolute justice can
sometimes drive a man to madness.
I've decided to let you escape.
I'm curious to see what
kind of flower will
sprout from the seed that's all protected?
You can bear a grudge against
whoever you like for this,
but at least you're still alive!
However, I do suggest
you keep a low profile.
I've drawn a path for
you on the sea with my
ice if you take the boat
and go straight ahead.
You'll reach land eventually oh
One last thing
I'm not your ally
If you do cause any trouble, I'll be
the first person to come after you.
My mom's here.
Can you help her?
No one will be saved.
If that pain is too great for you
to bear, then you may join them.
This library is the best in the world.
You like to read books?
Today is Robin's birthday.
Happy birthday from us at the library!
Your mama's a wonderful woman.
Oh, there's a wonderful place.
And as surely as we believe in the past,
we believe in the future
that you will inherit.
When you're feeling down, just laugh.
There ain't nothing a
good laugh can't fix.
It seems awfully silly
to laugh when you're sad.
Don't knock it till you try it.
Dad, she, she, she, she,
The sea's a fast place, so I guarantee
Hey!
Someday you'll find friends
who won't ever leave you!
Survivors?
No, I don't think so.
Hey! Huh?
Come here!
Look at the lake!
What?
That's insane!
How did all those books get here?
It can't be a coincidence.
Yeah, this is her.
That's definitely the girl.
Where did you find her?
Is she captured? No.
We were told to keep watch
for a suspicious girl.
We eventually found her on a
passenger ship northeast of Ohara.
Unfortunately, she knew
what we were after,
so she slipped away
before we could catch her.
Ah, she's got the devil's luck.
Back then, I'm sure I
saw her leaving Ohara.
The island was burning to ash,
but she somehow made it out
alone on a little rowboat.
Of course, i tried to chase
her, but all of a sudden,
the helm of our boat got stuck
like it was frozen in ice.
Sol probably helped her
escape before he died.
A scholar with the ability
to read the poneglyphs
is dangerous no matter
how young she may be.
Yeah.
I don't care what methods you use.
If we don't capture her immediately,
then this entire mission
will have been for nothing.
Seventy-nine million berries?
Why does an eight-year-old
child have such a high bounty?
They said she's one of
the devils of Ohara.
You know, those scholars who
are plotting to end the world?
Really?
I heard she's saying six
marine battleships, too.
She must have some kind of weird power.
Well, that explains the bounty.
The government forces and Navy
leaders are searching for her, too.
She probably wants to carry out the same
plan as the scholars that were executed.
If she's out for revenge,
then no one is safe.
We can't let a child
of the devil run wild.
Such a kind girl, thank
you for helping me out.
Sure, I'm grateful for any work I can get.
By the way, before we have our
dinner, some men are here to see you.
Don't let her get away.
Now, give me my money!
I told you where she was hiding, didn't I?
She may be small, but
she still works hard.
What's wrong?
Having trouble sleeping?
We have to get up early tomorrow
to go to work, so rest well. Kay.
She's sweet, but if we keep her around,
we could get in serious trouble.
Besides, just look at this bounty.
Honey!
She isn't in her room! Damn it!
She must have overheard us talking.
you're hungry sorry me too
seems we're both wanted by
the law robin i know all about
you work for me and i'll
make sure you never go hungry
captain the marines are after us where did
robin go Hand her over, dammit! Hooray!
That girl is bad luck!
A devil like you shouldn't even exist!
What?
Nico Robbins here? Where at?
Hunt her down!
Turn her into the government!
I can't believe it.
A Poneglyph.
Stay away!
I have nothing to sell
to the likes of you!
Look, I'm 16.
I'll do anything.
Please just allow me to join your group.
You betrayed me, you damn witch!
Nico Robin, I'd like you to assist me.
I've been told you can read Poneglyphs.
If you trigger a Buster Call,
everything will be destroyed.
That includes all of Eni's lobby.
And most likely, you as well.
Nonsense!
What are you saying?
They wouldn't kill a VIP like me!
I'm not falling for your bluff!
Twenty years ago, everything
was taken from me.
And many innocent lives were lost.
With one push of a button,
I summoned a terrible demon.
Now it rears its head again,
aiming its sights on the friends
I've searched so hard to find.
The more that I wish
for us to be together,
the more my ugly fate
bears its fangs at you.
Even now, no matter how far we sail, there's
an enemy that haunts me at every turn.
Because I'm facing the world
and all of its darkness.
First it was Aokiji, and now CP9.
I've dragged you into my
troubles twice already.
If it goes on and on like this,
no matter how kind you may be,
Someday you'll see me as a burden!
Someday you'll be forced to
betray me and throw me away!
That's what I'm most
afraid of! Understand?
That's why I didn't want you to rescue me!
If that's the only future I have,
I'd rather die to save me the pain!
Robin...
I never knew...
I see.
So that's it.
There you have it!
Yep, right on the mark!
What a sorry case!
Even if you make friends, all you can do
is drag them through the mud with you.
You can't win, pirates!
Look at this flag!
This symbol represents the
unity of over 170 nations,
a power that spans the four
seas and the Grand Line.
This is the world itself.
No matter how loud your bark may be, you
can't stand up to an enemy like that.
Just face it already.
Do you realize how strong
our organization is?
Do you realize how devoted
we are to capturing her?
If that's Robin's enemy,
then I know what to do.
Sniper King,
shoot down that flag.
Roger.
This is my new weapon, a massive
slingshot by the name of Kavuto.
Behold its awesome power!
Special attack, Firebird Star!
No way!
Mission complete.
Oh, now they've done it! Those idiots!
You can't fire on a government flag!
That's crazy!
Those pirates just declared war
against the world government!
You're all going to die!
You morons can't challenge the
entire world and expect to win! Yeah?
Bring it on!
Robin!
There's still something
I want to hear you say!
Tell me you want to live!
Robin.
I can live.
Face it!
Your whole existence
is nothing but a crime!
The whole world's against you, Robin!
You can't be allowed to live!
I never dared to wish
for something like that.
The world had denied me that hope.
I just want to die!
The sea's a vast place, so I guarantee...
Someday you'll find friends
who won't ever leave you.
Believe in Luffy.
But now, if I'm allowed to
say my wish just this once,
then I...
I want to live!
No!
Take me with you!
Take me away from here!
Oh, you guys, you're so awesome!
I love you!
Let's go!